<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quick COVID-19 Diagnostic</string>
    <string name="Info">
        This application help you checking if you are suspected to have COVID-19.
        \n\n
        This is not 100% accurate and suspected does not mean confirmed.
        \n\n
        The questions are based on symptoms of COVID-19 from CDC.
        \n\n
        Not suspected to have COVID-19 does not mean you are free from Social distance.
        \n\n
        This program is not responsible for any decision you make from this information.
        \n\n
        Use this program just as information, make sure to have conversation with your doctor.
    </string>
    <string name="credit">Made by - Hyeonwoo Heo, Sukmin Hong</string>
    <string name="question1">Question 1. Do you have fever or chill?</string>
    <string name="question2">Question 2. Do you cough often?</string>
    <string name="question3">Question 3. Are you having difficulty in breathing than usual?</string>
    <string name="question4">Question 4. Do you get tired easily(Fatigue)?</string>
    <string name="question5">Question 5. Do you have muscle or body aches?</string>
    <string name="question6">Question 6. Do you have headache?</string>
    <string name="question7">Question 7. Are you having loss of taste or smell?</string>
    <string name="question8">Question 8. Do you have congestion or runny nose?</string>
    <string name="question9">Question 9. Do you vomit or feel nausea often?</string>
    <string name="question10">Question 10. Do you have sore throat?</string>
    <string name="question11">Question 11. Do you have trouble breathing\n(extreme difficulty)?</string>
    <string name="question12">Question 12. Do you have persistent pain\n or pressure in the chest??</string>
    <string name="question13">Question 13. Do you feel disoriented and confusing?</string>
    <string name="question14">Question 14. Are you unable to wake up? or \n Are you unable to sleep?(Happened in 2 weeks)</string>
    <string name="question15">Question 15. Do you have Bluish lips or face?</string>
    <string name="ending2">
        You might be infected.
        \n
        You can stay home to see if you get more symptoms.
        \n
        But recommend to Go to near local emergency facility for diagnose test.
        \n
        Before you visit local emergency facility, Make sure to notify that you may have COVID-19
    </string>
    <string name="ending1">
        You do not seems like you are infected.
        \n
        Stay home and see if you get more symptoms.
        \n
        Keep social distance and stay home!
    </string>
    <string name="ending3">
        You are suspected to have COVID-19!
        \n
        Go to near local emergency facility for diagnose test.
        \n
        Before you visit local emergency facility, Make sure to notify that you may have COVID-19
    </string>
    <string name="ending4">
        CDC says You need medical care NOW!!!
        \n
        Go to local emergency facility!!
        \n
        Before you go, Call 911 or local emergency facility, and Nofity that you may have COVID-19.
    </string>
</resources>